manjam.eu 2016-02-10

# Privacy policy

This policy and any dispute or claim arising out of or in connection with it or its subject matter (including non-contractual disputes or claims) shall be governed by and construed in accordance with English and law. In the event there is a discrepancy between this English language version and any translated copies of the Privacy Policy, the English version shall prevail. 

###  Summary 

Please read our privacy policy carefully because it will tell you exactly how we are looking after your personal data. Here are the topics that we cover: 

  1. What information we collect and how we collect it 
  2. How we use the information and who we share it with 
  3. How you can access and update such information 
  4. How we protect the information we store about you 

###  Legal information 

HUBJET Limited ("we" or "us") is a company incorporated in Isle of Man under company number 000866L registered at 12 Mount Havelock, Douglas IM1 2QG. This privacy policy (the "Policy") is to let you know how we use personal information (‘personal data’ or ‘personal information’). 

This Policy applies to your use of the Manjam website at www.manjam.com ("Manjam"). We suggest you read it in conjunction with our Terms and Conditions of Use (the "Terms"). When you access or use Manjam, you agree to our Privacy Policy and you consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as we’ve set out in this Policy. 

We reserve the right to change our Policy at any time and without notice, so be sure to check this Policy regularly to understand how we use your information. 

####  IF YOU DO NOT ACCEPT AND AGREE WITH OUR PRIVACY POLICY THEN YOU MUST NOT ACCESS OR USE THE SITE. 

###  1\. Users and visitors to our site 

####  What information do you collect if I decide to register? 

To join Manjam you will have to complete our online registration form, where we ask you to provide us with information about you such as your name, your email address, your gender, your date of birth, your location details. Once you have created an account, we will automatically track certain information such as your IP address and your longitude and latitude if connecting using a device that supports such functionality. You will be able to correct or update your registration information by logging in to your account and editing your account settings. 

####  What information do you collect if I am under 18? 

You can only become a member of Manjam if your aged 18 or over (or the age of majority in the country in which you reside if that happens to be greater than 18). That means Manjam does not knowingly collect any information about children, minors or anyone under the age of majority. Nor do we knowingly market to children, minors or anyone under the age of 18. If you are less than 18 years old, we request that you do not submit information to us. If we become aware that a child, minor or anyone under the age of 18 has registered with us and provided us with personal information, we will take steps to terminate that person’s registration and delete their Profile information from Manjam. If we do delete a Profile because you violated our no children rules, we may retain your email and IP address to ensure that you do not try to get around our rules by creating a new Profile. 

####  Do you collect my personal information if I am not a member and just visit the site? 

No. We don’t collect any personal information about visitors to our site. If you do visit us without becoming a member, we will place session ID cookies on your computer. 

####  What do you do with personal information I have decided to post to the site? 

Manjam is designed to make it easy for you to find, connect and interact with other members of Manjam by posting information about yourself. You can also use our electronic messaging system, which allows you to communicate with other users. We recommend and encourage you (and all our members) to think carefully about the information they disclose about themselves. We also do not recommend that you put email addresses, instant messaging details, phone numbers, addresses, credit card details, national identity numbers, drivers’ licence details and other sensitive information in your Profile which is open to abuse and misuse. 

Please be careful about posting sensitive details about yourself on you Profile such as your religious denomination and health details. While you may voluntarily provide this information to us when you create your Profile, including your sexual preferences and ethnic background, there is no requirement to do so. Please remember that photographs or any video clips that you post on Manjam may reveal these kinds of sensitive personal data. Where you do upload and choose to tell us sensitive information about yourself, you are explicitly consenting to our processing your information and making this public to other users. 

When you post information about yourself or use the messaging, the amount of personal information you share is at your own risk. If you post anything that is inconsistent with our Terms and Conditions of Use, we reserve the right to terminate your account. 

####  What information is collected from me if I purchase premium services? 

If you decide to take advantage of any Manjam premium services, we collect any information necessary to process your payments as per your chosen payment method such as your name and address and or mobile number. We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties. 

####  Do you collect any other personal information about me? 

If you contact our Customer Support team we will receive your email address, your IP address as well as the information you send to us to help resolve your query. We will keep records of our communications with you, including any complaints that we receive from you about other users (and from other users about you). 

####  Will you contact me? 

In your account communication settings, you have the opportunity to opt-in or out of receiving emails from us about new message notifications or other purposes related to the use of the website. 

####  Do you use my personal information for any other purpose? 

We may use material that you post on the open access areas of Manjam in advertising and promotional materials or on our partner sites and partner products. You can opt-out at any time by hiding your Profile from non-members of the site in your account privacy settings. 

We use your personal information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms and Conditions of Use. 

####  How does the site use cookies? 

Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored on your computer, mobile phone or other device. They help sites recognise you and your preferences each time you visit and also help sites deliver their services and enable their functionality. 

Manjam collects and stores information by placing cookies on your computer or mobile device when you visit the site to enable site functionality. 

When you visit Manjam, a session ID cookie is placed on your computer or mobile device that only lasts while you’re visiting. 

We also place persistent cookies (also known an local storage devices) on members’ computers and mobile devices, so that Manjam remembers them and makes their login experience faster and easier when they return to the site. 

You may set your browser to block cookies and local storage devices, but if you do, you may not be able to access the features that Manjam offers. 

The types of cookies we store include: 

_Authentication_   
These cookies help us to identify if you have the correct permissions to access the site and allow you to use features such as communicating with other members and posting content. 

_Site services_   
These cookies provide the functionality that our Manjam members enjoy, such as your search preference, friend invitations, assisting with navigation and ensuring pages load up quickly and respond faster. 

_Analytics and research_   
We use Google Analytics to collect information about how visitors use the Manjam website. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited. 

###  2\. Friends and other Users 

####  When I post information about myself, what do the other users see? 

To ensure you get to meet as many people as possible on Manjam, other members get to see your user name and any information you post on your Profile, including public photos. Any information you choose to provide should reflect how much you want other people to know about you. You can choose to reveal your name to your friends and you can also choose to limit the information that other users see by adjusting your privacy settings in your account. 

####  What information do you collect about my friends and contacts? 

To make it easier to search and find friends and acquaintances on Manjam, users may search for other members using first and last name, email address and location. If you want to invite your friends and contacts to become a Manjam member, we will send an email invitation from Manjam in your name to your friends and contacts encouraging them to sign up to Manjam. If any of the individuals you have invited do not register within a few days, Manjam may occasionally send reminder emails to those individuals. Please remember you must not invite any children to join. You are responsible for ensuring that your friend has agreed to receiving a Manjam invite. 

When we send an email to your friend or contact, we store their name and email address. We do not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations. The friend may request the removal of their information from our database by clicking the ‘remove’ link in the email. Any such request will only apply to addresses we have at the time of the request and not to any addresses that the member/user provides to us later. 

###  3\. Third parties 

####  Do you sell my information to other parties? 

Not at all! We do not sell or rent out any personal information about you to any third party. 

####  Do you disclose my information to other parties? 

We may share aggregated information that includes your personal information (but which doesn’t identify you directly), together with other information including log data with third parties for industry analysis and demographic profiling and to deliver targeted advertising about other products and services. 

In particular, in relation to targeted advertising, we use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit Manjam. These companies may use information about your visits in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

We also wish to maintain a healthy community, and we will cooperate with all law enforcement inquiries and with all third parties to enforce their intellectual property or other rights. We may also disclose your personal information to government or law enforcement agencies, or private parties, as required by law when/or, in our sole discretion, we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our legal rights, or those of third parties and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on us. 

###  4\. Data storage 

Manjam is a global website operating through servers located in a number of countries around the world, including but not limited to, the United States, United Kingdom, France and The Netherlands. If you live in a country with data protection laws, the storage of your personal data may not provide you with the same protections as you enjoy in your country of residence. By submitting your personal information to us, you agree to the transfer of your personal information to, and storage and processing of your personal information in, any such countries and destinations. 

###  5\. Security 

####  How do you protect my personal information? 

We have implemented reasonable and appropriate security measures to protect and prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control, including your personal information. We use reasonable security measures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information such as secured servers using firewalls and encryption. Our technical experts at work hard to ensure your secure use of our site. 

While we take reasonable precautions against possible security breaches, no website or Internet transmission is completely secure and we cannot guarantee that unauthorised access, hacking, data loss, or other breaches will never occur. We urge you to take steps to keep your personal information safe (including your password) and to log out of your account after use. 

We cannot guarantee the security of your personal data while it is being transmitted to our site and any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information we have procedures and security features in place to try to prevent unauthorised access. 

####  How do I help keep my information secure? 

You may not disclose your password to any third parties or share it with any third parties. If you lose your password or give it out, your personal information may be compromised. If that happens, please report it to use. You must change your password immediately via your account settings. We cannot be held responsible for your failure to keep your password secure and failure to do so may violate our Terms and Conditions of Use. 

###  6\. Your rights 

####  How do I control my information? 

You can review and revise your profile information at any. You can create, modify and delete your personal information using the account settings when you edit your account. 

We strongly urge you to periodically change your password to help reduce the risk of unauthorised access to your account information. 

####  Can I deactivate or delete my Profile? 

You can cancel your account by choosing ‘cancel membership’ from your account settings when you are logged into your account. 

If you choose to cancel your account, it will be initially deactivated. This means that your Profile will no longer be available for others to view but your account will not be deleted. We save your Profile information in case you later decide to restore your account or if you cancelled your account by mistake and you later change your mind. Many users cancel their accounts for temporary reasons and in doing so expect us to maintain their information until they return to Manjam. You will therefore be able to restore your account and your Profile in its entirety within 12 months of cancelling it. 

After the 12 months expiration period, you will be sent an email informing you that your account will be permanently deleted from Manjam within 14 days. You have up to 14 days to login and restore your account. If you do not login within the 14-day period, your account is permanently deleted from Manjam. 

Please note: Even after you remove information from your profile or cancel your account, copies of that information may still be viewable and/or accessed on the Internet to the extent such information has been previously shared with others, or copied or stored by other users or to the extent such information has been shared with search engines. We cannot control this, nor do we accept any liability for this. 

Removed and deleted information may persist in backups, but will not be available to others. 

####  What happens if I do nothing? 

If you have not signed in to Manjam for 12 months, we may remove your Profile as part of our data cleansing process. 

###  Effective date 

The Policy was updated 1 January 2014.
